Many people know this, they know
that I am tweeting about my father's business, I am carrying
forward his pregnancy,
primarily for insurance, Mehr and
after I am able to carry on the business and
diamond ring for kids, in so many
such mistakes, many things I
learned from my mistakes, so you learn from mistakes
and move forward, so all those things happened like this, so
today I will share some things with you,
fifteen right side benefit
depression which I took in the last 15 years, I will
set an alarm, 15
area depression from the first, I have
sent many wrongs in the last 15 years, I will also
talk about which ones I took right, so the
purpose of sharing this is that those people who are
able to take their unemployed benefit depression family cover, are
not able to take it, many times they feel that it will go wrong, whether it is
wrong or right or not, so the
problem will be that you will get the insight that it does
not appear good too soon, sometimes
when you will think about this connected WhatsApp,
why did it happen, Hussain, but when this
thing happened, then automatically and reliance
Which one was Ramesh Chandra's wrong
because the defense keeps telling you this
in your life that you are what you are today because
you took some right and some wrong positions,
so I will share with you my husband right June,
in the beginning there is
no glimpse on the video, for them my name
is good quality and I tighten it
Shukla when I am practicing from elastic seniors
and laugh brother Saif year old Yash
and animation industry he goes
towards this video wheel drive differential
Tubelight's last fifteen years so first
and rise against reservations for rent in
office beta from small home office, I
cleaned the room of the house, used to update development etc., used to
work phone, from today I will
talk to you and 16 years ago, this would
not have caused cancer, but father had
made a room in the house, got it set up from there, so
we are extending it a bit, team
hair curry and sugar and thought of making it possible, so we did not
make our country by making this interesting investment to buy an office, so I did
not do it and I did office there,
after that when we today  If we melt it, then it means
such a complete function send if I operate
that Rans vs Bahubali
calculation to the company's answer is Amit
proved to be the right function reaction second
Chandrabhushan if it was taken correctly it was chest
waxing mutual funds to get so I
started investing in mutual funds
when I so this website Eid & 2017 is
very early this video would have been more line it would have been
better if it had been done sooner but still better late than never to do
something so there is a
possibility send my photos I will
directly get compounding benefit NCB money after
growing up I tell this to my children
and further I tell this to the young generation also that
tuition start with a little small amount, that is you can
start as per the smallest amount, you
can start shaving by getting ₹500
but definitely do ghee on it and
teach the children also to do like this in future when they
grow up and earn 2560 then they will have a
verification a corpus will have been created which
like us from 500 or thousands per month they will get back  If it gets
created then just give it, it
needs to be told that we should start matching on gas,
thirdly, through opening bank account,
further we have opened bank account for children, as the children have
job interviews, the principal who is mine, is
from father's side, Bigg Boss association
couples, so now the children should subscribe
to their channel along with the children, this is how it happens,
whatever happens, the association
creates them, that is why I have made a
separate bank account, Malviya ji, the same
money was studying in class, at home I do
n't know where it goes, so there was a trick here
that if we had a bank account, then your
printer money is for them and
why not multiply it, I mean there is
no use in crackers in the bag, if you
grind them and multiply then
move towards Tubelight, it is special, snacks,
translations of investing in the care,
Apple MacBook Air, in one
and a half-two years of my career shopping,
I have bought a lot of HP laptops, so today that
means I use a lot of laptops, every
one and a half year I
also bought laptops, big or small notebooks, for 20 minutes and they stop,
so  I mean, in two years, Ramesh,
I am saying more,
in one and a half years, that area
was responding, its light computer Divya, I had to
buy a new one, I had to hit the button, so it was
achieved, then I had
handed over the 8th in 2012,
why didn't I take the audition earlier, you are great, it is great, right from the time I
bought it, I have been
using it till today and it is so comfortable and I did
not need to change it after that, since then
I have been working on it and it has become
very comfortable, my life has also become very comfortable, my
productivity has increased,
my work has become easier, morning password,
so investing in it is very important
because it suggests you to grow, so if
you keep going with the same old things, then you will
not be
able to move forward, so if you leave traditional cigarettes and have to
invest somewhere, then this is that
coincidence, it is a good phone, it is the
best, it is useful, if
you are a graphic professional, then definitely it is useful, so
next is that I should take
some health insurance etc.  I will
talk about that time, answer 15 years ago when two
Lal Singh soldiers were included in you, it was
believed that the deposit was
already enough and how much would be needed,
we started pelting stones, so he
grew up and after winning, he increased it, so he kept
eating online only Chandrabhushan
because if I look back, if
you discuss while sleeping, if any
medical configuration occurs, any
lifestyle change occurs, then you do
not have the scope to increase your understanding, sorry, this
company has a choice, it installs you, it will
not increase it, Matki Smile,
that we know that if ever there is a need for our deposit insurance, then
we will have to withdraw it by serving, the
zonal committee will take care of getting,
so my settings will be correct,
so this cleaning liquid health
insurance 18.12 increases now and no claim
bonus and the remaining balance increases, if something comes under its control,
then it controls you, so the
next thing is that our liability is very less, it is
negligible, I used to say that
whatever you have  Spend that much, that means the more
you are rich, the more you should expand
beyond that, Prasad, happiness, never sorrow, there is
no cat in the edit, time is water,
use credit or debit card, use what you have,
why do you have to borrow and use it,
but you are different from China, now we have to use credit card, for that you
get reward points for it, but in a
short time limit, we make the
payment in that 3250 desktop rapid, which is what
you get in rebuke, and that is what I would
like to tell my family, Vital Sinus Daughter,
my liabilities are also negligible because
when I am unable to sleep at night, I am
putting my liabilities on the side, I am alone and I am unable to sleep, then chapter
note how it is, use of intelligence and preservation
like routine, Jatin, as much as is needed, I am having a little
humor on my face, I do
not have too many liabilities, so it is known
that that matter which will take care of,
we cannot put too much on our plate, that
means we do not have so much surplus, if the
liabilities increase then they get trapped
in debt trap, people
lose their health  The liabilities of mail message solution that
we took to build up
five years back when I realized that
in many homes
where there is no clarity about
which hero is for whom, here you have
inheritance. If you
don't decide your property by inheritance and decide to
whom you want to transfer it to as per your wish, then there will be
duty of Honey Singh,
Bhim Singh and actresses around you
with your friends. If you want a scene, that is, a fight, then you should
tune for yourself, for the
children of your aunt's house,
which is legalized, but when Anuj
Dhar Cotton does it successfully, we wrote 5 years ago and
told here that people of Delhi say,
what is the need so quickly, so for the purpose,
you have Bittu or 125, so you don't know,
but this thing, a relative woman's no problem will not
come anywhere, so do that
[Music],
Midnight Children, you should
skill yourself, so from time to time I thought that
I should buy other things but it is
very important to match yours.  Your growth card
and other things are starting to happen, the
world around you is going on like this, so you will have to
ignore it somewhere to be happy with it, so you will have to improve your
skills as well, so if for some
time I also started doing my research,
enrolling in many cards, in
these 2 years digitally and really by
enrolling in many questions, increase your knowledge,
your focus and basically
increase your area of ​​activities and I have been doing
infection and depression in the village, my
weakness for so many years, then life is
important in these things, whatever other things you are mashing,
your time is getting delayed in other things, then it is
very important to match it automatically with
your body needs and aspirations of
investing in technology, so from the very beginning
when I started investing in technology, I had said in my
professional life that there should be minimum paper
work and if we do not embrace technology for eight to 10 years, 15 years, 20
years, then at that time
many software companies will get affected, if at that time
people of the land industry  What is the need,
I am getting destroyed at the same time, it is
injured, it will go away now, it will go away in 2 years or it will go away,
but if I talk about 10 years, or
20 years, and share it on a
long-term basis, meaning because this YouTube
relationship business and long term work,
it is not a translation of this practice,
but the four-inch policy has become tough, no,
slave, it keeps going, till now we have
three or four generations of Shamli, all of them have been returned,
grandfather, his son, his son
and grandson too, but if it had happened then this generation's bill, the
structure of the constitution, at this time when there were those who were
benefited, there our lighting should also be made
and tell about their life and when the blast happened for type, at that
time there was
no hard work of the public in your war, how will the office run
forever, we can do virtual office,
that became possible only after long, we
realized that we are working from home, till now it never
felt like how should we work, morning
day greetings, every system in plates,
through technology, the entire team is connected
and is running very well, so somewhere  There is no
problem, the next cancer patient I
took is vested in your details
of ₹5000 would have been 10 grams, I had also matched, so
when we got married in 2015, the
money was collected from such schemes, then also we have to keep some
money on the side, don't make a line, as my God, it will be useful in the
future, so keep a circle on it, by
doing this your when I see
that horse time investment Holi, today I am,
see, I feel very happy that I had
taken ₹5000 and what is the rate today, so title,
this romantic life level, there is some satisfaction
that Kartikeya NewsX and
how much property he has, he grew up,
we have some specific good start, so that is that at the
right time, whisker,
if that test should be used, we were going to sit, then I do
n't even know where the Next
Launcher which we took, we have opened the children and
now we have made an economic vision in the world, this happens
many times, how will you make the children understand this,
grains
in the light bill and a lot of parents are not even told about it,
along with that we also started chilli and  We make them
sit and tell them once
what we are doing, how we are doing it,
where is the measurement, where is it
not, be aware about it and insurance
policies, the children know everything, secondly, when we
talk to the children, it is also surprising that
their knowledge is very good and it
also helps them in our digital meetings, if we want to
invest in Malaysia, then we make our children
sit and talk about whether they
want to invest and this is objective, that is why they want to do it, then through this the
children have a complete opinion, a complete interview,
why do you want to invest, is it
active, that you do not need liquidity, that is, to do
this gap, there was a complete discussion, that is, it was
good when the children saw the government and the scientists
talked to them about finance by playing the presence of this thing, I make the
children small, every year in 2017
705 Tuesday come to the bank, when I used to go to the
supermarket, I used to do my grocery shopping, then only
simple steps, what is this
and what is this and what happens, if
our children  Ask them what is a high
loan like this, I mean, with my
interview with the children, I bought a CBC, with the corpse,
when I asked the children about the lineage version, the
price was famous, meaning
their knowledge and what they saw around them,
like then what are you doing,
now what are you talking about, should the
fuel be a turn of humor, the importance
of investment agency point, there should be
insurance, it has been a few days,
so you will know that in the future, their
life will also be good, their personal life will also be good, right now
our focus is on the
coordination with the businessmen and complete
involvement in everything, in the functions, it will
help your children also,
[Music] Do it,
make your friends, I still do budgeting in remote villages,
one person is a system,
if you saw a statue of Akshay Kumar,
he had kept that feedback, it was for
mother's eye operation, sister's wedding,
attending questions like this, till the conflict of mind, for this
goal, for the solution, 0, I am
absolutely free, you can save here, I mean, there are
many applications, you  You
can make it but I still stop it friend if you
maintain its note then the difference of Tubelight
with month I
know this is a pencil, divide it first
so you test Prabhjeet or you can do it
from there first play online, you can
wear casual wear, so I am painting now, so
batting actually health, you have
this road near you Malthone Reliance,
how can you increase your setting and
you have fried it well from the second time, as you
know, where should the money be saved
because as soon as we hear this, we discuss, nothing is
left, so here this
lever is that there is an advantage of chatting, I
mean quality, I knew whether
these stones are that you can light and so that he is a
child, you can do it from here, so
last but not least is the old age pension
emergency kit which we had made from here 5 years ago,
which the customers also say that
whatever important documents and
drops of yours, but whatever packing carrier you can carry with you, then
whatever important
papers are there in it, your ID  Proof is needed, legal
documents, property,
liability in it, whatever important function
side is there in it and the topic basic document
which is for important ad, then they are
definitely in this box and are always there, so if ever
needed in emergency, you can put it in the
side box, 2 help, one, it has been
consolidated, whatever important thing will be there,
secondly, we know that that thing is needed in emergency,
okay, one beat, that 20% zone enemy,
then I thought of sharing it with you, so
my good descendants were Rajasthan solution, which
I think, so I thought of sharing it with you,
you can also take the question site,
so you can also reach right,
write depression, ideal rally help, on one side from where we will
run the mathematics, so that we had done this, Hussain
is present because of that, so it will feel very good, if
you see, then write it now, many devotees including you should
share it, I will very soon
tell you about my wrong Anite shoes1,
as I said that we learn from mistakes, so
I will talk to you about that also
and anything of your fashion  Insurance from 100ml
Regarding anything you
want to participate in, you will see it daily, a reminder when it comes,
please subscribe button so that you keep getting the diet
circulation at the right time, thank you
for watching my video and take
specific care